Ren d'Harnoncourt Papers
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series VIII: Exhibitions arranged and directed by d'Harnoncourt, 1941-1968
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Pan American-Grace Airways, Inc. (Panagra), 1953-54; RDH correspondence with Louis Garcia, public relations director of Panagra which helped with the transportation of items lent by people in South America. Scripts of WQXR radio commercials broadcast by Panagra advertising the Andes exhibition. (Folder VIII.24)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Heeramaneck, Nasli, 1954; RDH letter to Nasli Heeramaneck, lender to the exhibition (10/28/54). (Folder VIII.25)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Heye Foundation, Museum of the American Indian, 1953-54; RDH correspondence with George Heye and E.K. Burnett, assistant director of the Heye Foundation. (Folder VIII.26)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Publicity, Correspondence, copies of programs, press clippings. Copy of article on the exhibition by Holger Cahill in Art Digest (2/15/54). (Folder VIII.27)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Cleveland Museum of Art, 1953-55; RDH and Mildred Constantine correspondence with William Milliken, director, and others at the Cleveland Museum of Art, lender to the exhibition. (Folder VIII.28)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Bliss, Robert Woods, RDH and Mildred Constantine correspondence with Robert Woods Bliss, lender to the exhibition. Mr. Blisss collection was at the time on loan to the National Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. (Folder VIII.29)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Museum fur Volkerkunde, Munich, 1953-55; RDH and others correspondence with the Museum fur Volkerkunde, Munich, lender to the exhibition. (Partly in German) (Folder VIII.30)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- American Museum of Natural History, 1953-54; RDH correspondence with Dr. Harry Shapiro, chairman, dept. of anthropology, and Junius Bird, associate curator of archaeology, American Museum of Natural History, lender to the exhibition. (Folder VIII.31)
  - Ancient Arts of the An des - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1953-54; RDH and Mildred Constantine correspondence with NAR - lender to the exhibition - and with people in his office. (Folder VIII.32)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Simkhovitch, Vladimir, 1954; Brief RDH correspondence with Vladimir Simkhovitch about his collection. (Folder VIII.33)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Speyer, Darthea, 1953-54; RDH correspondence with Darthea Speyer, lender to the exhibition. (Folder VIII.34)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Strong, William Duncan, 1954; RDH letters to William Duncan Strong, Columbia University, lender to the exhibition. (Folder VIII.35)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Calderon, Augusto, 1953-54; RDH correspondence with Augusto Alvarez Calderon who helped with arrangements for the exhibition in Lima - particularly relating to objects lent by Rafael Larco Hoyle. (Folder VIII.36)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Ambassador Fernando Berckemeyer, 1953-54; RDH correspondence with Ambassador Fernando Berckemeyer, Peruvian ambassador to the U.S., who helped with official arrangements for the exhibition in Peru. (Folder VIII.37)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Opening, 1953-54; Some correspondence, lists of guests at dinners held on opening night, 1/26/54. Attendance records. 1 TLS NAR - RDH (11/16/53) saying that he is thrilled about the Andes show, and would like to give a dinner in RDHs honor on the night of the opening. (Folder VIII.38)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Chicago Natural History Museum, 1953-55; RDH and Mildred Constantine correspondence with Colonel Clifford Gregg, director, and Donald Collier, Chicago Natural History Museum, lender to the exhibition. (Folder VIII.39)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Art Institute of Chicago, 1953-55; RDH and Mildred Constantine correspondence with Daniel Catton Rich, director, Alan Sawyer and Meyric Rogers of the Art Institute of Chicago about loans to the exhibition from the collection of Dr. Hans Gaffron. (Folder VIII.40)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Textile Museum, Washington, D.C., 1953-55; Brief correspondence about Peruvian textiles lent by the Textile Museum. (Folder VIII.41)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- University of Pennsylvania Museum, 1953-55; RDH, Mildred Constantine, and Dorothy Dudley correspondence with Alfred Kidder II, associate director, and others at the University Museum, University of Pennsylvania, lender to the exhibition. (Folder VIII.42)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Wise, John, 1953-54; Correspondence with John Wise Ltd., lender to the exhibition. Two textiles lent by John Wise were on permanent loan to the Cleveland Museum of Art. (Folder VIII.43)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Peabody Museum, Harvard University, 1953-55; RDH and Mildred Constantine correspondence with Dr. Joseph Brew, director, Dr. Samuel Lothrop, and others at the Peabody Museum, lender to the exhibition. (Folder VIII.44)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Public Response, 1954; Letters to RDH about the Andes exhibition. 1 TLS Max Weber - RDH (2/24/54 - incorrectly dated 2/24/53) praising the exhibition. (Folder VIII.45)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Label Preparations, 1954; Andes exhibition labels and notes. (Folder VIII.46)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Label Preparations, 1954; Notes for label preparation. (Folder VIII.47)
  - Ancient Arts of the Andes- Exhibition Book, 1953; RDH correspondence and notes about the book accompanying the Andes exhibition. Drafts of introduction written by RDH. (Folder VIII.48)
  - Indian Art of the United States, 1941; Material on the Indian Art exhibition which was shown at MoMA from Jan. 22 - April 27, 1941, and afterwards became a circulating exhibition. Program for Lectures on Indian Art given in conjunction with the exhibition by RDH and Frederic H. Douglas, 1/28 - 2/13/41. (Folder VIII.49)
  - Indian Art of the United States, 1941; Material on the Indian Art exhibition. Photographs of some of the objects in the exhibition. (Folder VIII.50)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso- Labels and wall text, 1967; Correspondence and notes for the preparation of labels for the exhibition of Picassos sculpture, Oct.11, 1967-Jan. 1, 1968. Copies of labels and wall text. (Folder VIII.51)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Copies of drawings by RDH. (Folder VIII.52)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Copies of drawings by RDH. (Folder VIII.53)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Copies of drawings by RDH. (Folder VIII.54)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Two memos from RDH to Alicia Legg about the installation of the exhibition. Copies of drawings by RDH. (Folder VIII.55)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Labels and written information about the installation of the exhibition. (Folder VIII.56)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Copies of obsolete floor plans. (Folder VIII.57)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Floor plans. (Folder VIII.58)
  - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967; Floor plans. (Folder VIII.59)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings- Lenders, Foreign, 1958; RDH correspondence with foreign lenders to the Seurat exhibition which was shown from Mar. 24-Apr.15, 1958 and from May 1-11, 1958. Many of the letters are to lenders following the fire on April 15. (Folder VIII.60)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings, 1958; Inter-office memos about loans for the exhibition. Two letters praising RDHs installation of the Seurat show: TLS John Maxon, director, Rhode Island School of Design - RDH (4/3/58) TLS Louis Carre - RDH (4/4/58) who writes that Some day I hope you will publish a book on your magnificent installations. (Folder VIII.61)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings- Lenders, Domestic, 1958; RDH correspondence with lenders to the Seurat exhibition in the U.S. Many of the letters are to lenders following the fire on April 15, 1958 (Folder VIII.62)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings- Lenders, Domestic, 1958; RDH correspondence with lenders to the Seurat exhibition in the U.S. Copies of loan receipts. (Folder VIII.63)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings- Opening, 1958; RDH correspondence about the preview and dinners on the opening night of the exhibition, March 24, 1958. (Folder VIII.64)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings, 1958; Plan of first installation of the Seurat exhibition. (Folder VIII.65)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings, 1957-58; RDH correspondence with Daniel Catton Rich, director, Art Institute of Chicago, about the Seurat exhibition, which was co-sponsored by the Art Institute and shown there before coming to New York. Dorothy Dudley correspondence with Margaret Bush, registrar, Art Institute of Chicago. Press releases. (Folder VIII.66)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings, 1958; Copies of lists of lenders who were sent cables following the fire on April 15, 1958. (Folder VIII.67)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings- Reinstallation, 1958; Photographs and wall labels of the reinstallation of the Seurat exhibition after the fire. (Folder VIII.68)
  - Seurat Paintings and Drawings- Reinstallation, 1958; RDH original plan and drawings for the reinstallation of the Seurat exhibition after the fire. Press releases. (Folder VIII.69)
  - Steichen the Photographer, 1959-61; Includes RDH, MW, Edward Steichen, and Grace Mayer correspondence about the exhibition,Steichen the Photographer, March 28-May 30,1961. (Folder VIII.70)
  - Timeless Aspects of Modern Art, 1949; Photographs of objects in the Walter C. Baker Collection of Greek and Roman Art, some of which were used in the exhibition,Timeless Aspects of Modern Art, shown Nov. 16-Jan. 23, 1949. List of objects in the Baker Collection. Four photographs from John Wise, Ltd. (Folder VIII.71)
- Series IX: Art of Installation, 1930-1974
  The material in this series relates to a book that d'Harnoncourt was working on at the time of his death on the subject of his exhibition installation. It includes many of the original drawings that he used both in preparation for an exhibition, and during the actual installation. After d'Harnoncourt's death, Mordechai Omer worked on the project, but the book was never published. Also included is the manuscript of Omers text for the book, and memos about the progress of the project.
  - Subseries A: MoMA exhibitions at MoMA
    - Indian Art of the United States, 1941; Copies of photographs of the exhibition shown at MoMA Jan. 22-April 27, 1941. Black and white slides of individual objects shown in the exhibition. (Folder IX.A.1)
    - Indian Art of the United States, RDHs preliminary sketches of plans and elevations (used as basis of key plans and elevations drawn by the Indian Arts and Crafts Board). Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.2*)
    - Road to Victory, 1942; Copy photograph of model of the exhibition. (Folder IX.A.3)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of maps of the areas covered in the exhibition. (Folder IX.A.4)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: Solomon Islands. (Folder IX.A.5)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of installations, including sections on New Ireland, Polynesia: Fiji; Polynesia: Easter Island, New Zealand, Micronesia. (Folder IX.A.6)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of installations, including sections on Australia, Papuan Gulf, Dutch New Guinea, Huon Gulf. (Folder IX.A.7)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Australia. (Folder IX.A.8)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Britain. (Folder IX.A.9)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Guinea and Huon Gulf. (Folder IX.A.10)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Micronesia: Caroline Islands, and other islands. (Folder IX.A.11)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Caledonia. (Folder IX.A.12)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Hebrides. Also a scale drawing of objects from Melanesia: New Hebrides. (Folder IX.A.13)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Guinea, Papua and Papuan Gulf. (Folder IX.A.14)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of maps and cultural areas. (Folder IX.A.15)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original lists of major regions. (Folder IX.A.16)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of installations of several areas, including Easter Island, Hawaii, Fiji, Sepik River. (Folder IX.A.17)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Guinea, Sepik Area. (Folder IX.A.18)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Guinea, Dutch New Guinea. (Folder IX.A.19)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Guinea, Massim Area. (Folder IX.A.20)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: Trobriand Islands. (Folder IX.A.21)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Polynesia: Fiji Islands. (Folder IX.A.22)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Polynesia: Central Polynesia. (Folder IX.A.23)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Polynesia: Marquesas Islands. (Folder IX.A.24)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Guinea, Torres Straits. (Folder IX.A.25)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Polynesia: New Zealand. (Folder IX.A.26)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Polynesia: Hawaii. (Folder IX.A.27)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Polynesia: Easter Island. (Folder IX.A.28)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: New Ireland. (Folder IX.A.29)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original drawings of individual pieces from Melanesia: Admiralty Islands. (Folder IX.A.30)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original floor plans of installations. (Folder IX.A.31)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original scale drawings of groups of objects. (Folder IX.A.32)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; RDH original scale drawings of groups of objects. (Folder IX.A.33)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Production: lists of production orders including pedestals, colors for pedestals, installation devices, wall captions and maps. (Folder IX.A.34)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Press releases about the exhibition. (Folder IX.A.35)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Drafts of captions for the individual objects, including names of lenders. Wall labels and drafts of labels about the different areas. (Folder IX.A.36)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Copies of installation photographs. (Folder IX.A.37)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Copies of installation and event photographs. (Folder IX.A.38)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Watercolor of installation. Oversize, see box 134. (Folder IX.A.39*)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Color slides of installations. (Folder IX.A.40)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Color slides of installations. (Folder IX.A.41)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Color slides of installations. (Folder IX.A.42)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Black and white slides of installations. (Folder IX.A.43)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Black and white slides of installations. (Folder IX.A.44)
    - Arts of the South Seas, 1946; Transparencies of installations. (Folder IX.A.45)
    - Henry Moore, 1947; RDH original drawings of individual objects and installations. (Folder IX.A.46)
    - Henry Moore, 1947; RDH original drawings of individual objects and installations. (Folder IX.A.47)
    - Henry Moore, 1947; Copies of installation photographs. (Folder IX.A.48)
    - Gabo - Pevsner, 1948; Copy memo Monawee Allen - Dorothy Dudley (9/24/47) of notes taken at Gabos studio. (Folder IX.A.49)
    - Gabo - Pevsner, 1948; RDH original drawings of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.50)
    - Gabo - Pevsner, 1948; RDH original drawings of installation views. (Folder IX.A.51)
    - Gabo - Pevsner, 1948; Copies of installation photos. (Folder IX.A.52)
    - Elie Nadelman, 1948; RDH original drawings of individual pieces. (Folder IX.A.53)
    - Elie Nadelman, 1948; RDH original drawings of groupings. (Folder IX.A.54)
    - Elie Nadelman, 1948; RDH original drawings of ground plan. (Folder IX.A.55)
    - Elie Nadelman, 1948; RDH original drawings of theme panels. (Folder IX.A.56)
    - Elie Nadelman, 1948; RDH original list of pedestals, and some drawings of pedestals. (Folder IX.A.57)
    - Elie Nadelman, 1948; Copies of installation photos. Copy of preliminary list of works to be included in the exhibition. (Folder IX.A.58)
    - Elie Nadelman, 1948; Floor plan - blue print of MoMA 3rd floor galleries. Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.59*)
    - Timeless Aspects of Modern Art, 1948-49; RDH original drawings of installations. (Folder IX.A.60)
    - Timeless Aspects of Modern Art, 1948-49; Copies of installation photos. (Folder IX.A.61)
    - Timeless Aspects of Modern Art, 1948-49; Floor plan, MoMA 1st floor, drawn by Jean Volkmer from RDH sketch. (Folder IX.A.62)
    - Timeless Aspects of Modern Art, 1948-49; Analysis of the exhibition by Mordechai Omer. (Folder IX.A.63)
    - Modern Art in Your Life, 1949; RDH original drawings of installations. (Folder IX.A.64)
    - Modern Art in Your Life, 1949; RDH original drawings of ground plan, perspective views. (Folder IX.A.65)
    - Modern Art in Your Life, 1949; Copies of installation photos, including photos of RDH taken during the installation of the exhibition. (Folder IX.A.66)
    - Modern Art in Your Life, 1949; Analysis of the exhibition by Mordechai Omer. (Folder IX.A.67)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; RDH original drawings of individual objects - preliminary list. (Folder IX.A.68)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; RDH original drawings of individual objects - preliminary list. (Folder IX.A.69)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; RDH original drawings of individual objects - preliminary list. (Folder IX.A.70)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Copies of installation photos. (Folder IX.A.71)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Copies of installation photos. (Folder IX.A.72)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Copies of installation photos. (Folder IX.A.73)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; One plan of installation. Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.74*)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Slides of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.75)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Slides of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.76)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Slides of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.77)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Color prints of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.78)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Negatives of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.79)
    - Ancient Arts of the Andes, 1954; Transparencies of installations. (Folder IX.A.80)
    - Seurat Paintings and Drawings, 1958; RDH original plan for distribution of paintings and drawings. Original drawings of installations. (Folder IX.A.81)
    - Jean Arp: A Retrospective, 1958; RDH original drawings of installation plans. Also list with detailed information about pedestals. (Folder IX.A.82)
    - Jean Arp: A Retrospective, 1958; RDH original drawings of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.83)
    - Jean Arp: A Retrospective, 1958; Exhibit partition plan. Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.84*)
    - Jean Arp: A Retrospective, 1958; MoMA 3rd floor plan (Philip Johnson Associates). Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.85*)
    - Jean Arp: A Retrospective, 1958; Exhibit partition plan, ceiling troffer locations (Philip Johnson Associates). Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.86*)
    - Jean Arp: A Retrospective, 1958; Copies of photographs of RDH and Jean Arp from Life magazine (10/27/58). (Folder IX.A.87)
    - Jean Arp: A Retrospective, 1958; Copies of checklists, photographs, and plans. (Folder IX.A.88)
    - Recent Sculpture USA, 1959; RDH original drawings: scale drawings and plans. (Folder IX.A.89)
    - Recent Sculpture USA, 1959; Original exhibit partition plan. Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.90*)
    - Recent Sculpture USA, 1959; Copies of installation photographs and plans. (Folder IX.A.91)
    - Recent Sculpture USA, 1959; Copies of installation photographs from MoMA exhibition album. (Folder IX.A.92)
    - Steichen the Photographer, 1961; RDH original installation drawings. (Folder IX.A.93)
    - Steichen the Photographer, 1961; Installation photographs of the exhibition. (Folder IX.A.94)
    - Steichen the Photographer, 1961; RDH sketch of floor plan and distribution of objects. Oversize, see flat file at MoMA QNS. (Folder IX.A.95*)
    - Chagall - The Jerusalem Windows, 1961-62; Copy photograph of the installation. (Folder IX.A.96)
    - Art of the Asmat- The Collection of Michael C. Rockefeller, 1962; Press release (9/11/62) about the exhibition, which was shown in the MoMA Sculpture Garden under the auspices of the Museum of Primitive Art. (Folder IX.A.97)
    - Art of the Asmat, 1962; Copy photographs of the exhibition and of the pavilion in which it was housed. (Folder IX.A.98)
    - Art of the Asmat, 1962; Copy photographs of the installation. (Folder IX.A.99)
    - Art of the Asmat, 1962; 8 plans. Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.100*)
    - Rodin, 1963; RDH original scale drawings of individual objects (Folder IX.A.101)
    - Rodin, 1963; RDH original drawings of installations. (Folder IX.A.102)
    - Rodin, 1963; Lists of pedestals. (Folder IX.A.103)
    - Rodin, 1963; RDH original notes. (Folder IX.A.104)
    - Rodin, 1963; Copy installation photos. (Folder IX.A.105)
    - Rodin, 1963; RDH original sketch of ground plan and distribution of objects. Oversize, see flat file at MoMAQNS. (Folder IX.A.106*)
    - Edward Steichen Photography Center, 1966; Copy photographs of the installation of the Edward Steichen Photography Center. (Folder IX.A.107)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; RDH original drawings of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.108)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Floor plans. (Folder IX.A.109)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; RDH original notes on cases and pedestals. (Folder IX.A.110)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Copies of RDH notes on cases and pedestals. (Folder IX.A.111)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Copies of installation photographs taken by George Cserna. (Folder IX.A.112)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Copies of installation photographs taken by George Cserna. (Folder IX.A.113)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; RDH original drawings of installations. (Folder IX.A.114)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; RDH original floor plans, and some copies. (Folder IX.A.115)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Photograph and slides of the posters outside the Museum. (Folder IX.A.116)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Copy drawings of individual objects. (Folder IX.A.117)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Copy drawings of installations. (Folder IX.A.118)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Copy drawings of installations. (Folder IX.A.119)
    - The Sculpture of Picasso, 1967-68; Copy drawings of installations (Folder IX.A.120)